Arsenal match he's taken charge of
Liverpool games a couple of times this
season we've already mentioned him big
game for Harvey Elli a big chance for
him yeah it's a huge chance for him
still only 20 years of age the boys in
the studio mentioned him earlier got
great talent I think he really relished
this role today because I think he suits
that role better in forward positions
can score a goal and obviously likes
creating them as well and it's a huge
five or six weeks for this guy
and an opportunity for Kai havitz we
think as part of the attack he has been
playing well in Midfield of late yeah a
lot will depend on him today he's going
to think we think we'll play in that
that Center forward role he will like to
to to drop deep but then it's up for
others to try and run past him cuz at
times it can be a lonely role if players
are not prepared to do that four goals
in his last nine so he should be
confident who have suffered the Los of a
loved one through the a we're just about
ready to go
join us Liverpool playing in a shade
that's described officially as space
purple well there's a new
one and it is going to be Harvey Elliot
with the first kick of the
match they met as recently as the 23rd
of December it was one one at anfield in
the Premier League Arsenal in front in
the fourth minute and when Liverpool
were last here last season arsenal were
ahead after 58 seconds so watch from the
[Applause]
start Ben
White the numbers on the back of the
[Applause]
shirt just to make your job
easier yeah the binoculars were out
prematch and white HS it up towards
habits it was M alist who jumped with
[Applause]
it turn back to Aaron ramale every time
he starts in goal for Arsenal there will
be a magnifying glass upon his
performance yeah I heard the guys in the
studio talking about the situation
regarding the keepers at Arsenal all I
ever wanted to do was know I was playing
uh and mentally if you if you not aware
of that then I think it makes it very
difficult in that situation particularly
for a
goalkeeper in towards
Nunes looked as though it might break
for gakpo but it's been cleared by Kio
and Liverpool have the
[Applause]
throw Ator replaced at the break at
Fulham in the last game a week ago yeah
I think it's really important for him to
get off to a good start because when
that happens confidence dip need a touch
or two of the ball and good
ones that's one player who will be
relieved that moal isn't part of
Liverpool Squad absolutely
yeah nun challenges but CA kept it away
from him and Gabrielle turns it back to
ramsdale
again Arsenal have lost the last two
they're three without a win only one
winning that last six but what about
this for a chance and Allison has gone
back and been beaten
into the side of the goal it was a great
opportunity for ree Nelson played in
over the top well I mentioned the
confidence of players what better way to
start for that guy and ra ramsdale what
a
pass and what a run as well comes in
from the inside there ree Nelson in
between the fullback and the center half
and that's a really good opportunity
just a bit of a heavy touch to go around
the goalkeeper but what a pass that was
from ramsdale
should be one
up Allison M
aliser and returned again to the
Liverpool
keeper I would think nicolar tetta's
eyes would have widened at that as well
noting the pace of Nelson against the
two Liverpool center backs we actually
got it between Trent I think it was and
and canate was a really clever run timed
it to perfection
now here's Elliot D Nunes in the middle
trying to stay on
side and Elliot is bungled to the floor
Liverpool will get a free kick and a
chance to put the ball into the Arsenal
box well if the first three minutes or
anything to go by we're in for a good
game aren't we looks that
way R Elliot starting brightly his 50th
start for
Liverpool scored in his last two FA Cup
ties got the
winner at wolves in the third round
replay a year
ago and still only 20 still only 20 and
both teams have a 16-year-old on the
bench
today remember those days nope long long
[Applause]
ago Alexander Arnold
delivers nobody has to bother themselves
with that one then white will watch it
all the way
out not very often that happens is it
talking the quality of
[Applause]
trend Captain's armband
today throw herberts was hoping to win
it mallister was up against him here's
Jones
now that will be an Arsenal
[Applause]
throw good burst of noise from the
Liverpool supporters there are just over
7 a half
thousand of them
today normal away allocation at Arsenal
is
3,000 every one of those 7,600 tickets
have been taken up
[Applause]
white saw the opportunity to find
jino CA does well against
Nunes one back by
white sacka gets away from The
Challenge
Nelson didn't get it quickly
enough and Arsenal have to go backwards
to come forwards again thought he should
have shot
Lord of God he had the opportunity to
open up for him I think he needed to
pass
out
rice white to sacka and Gomez pokes out
of foot and gets the ball out of
play both teams have had bright
moments positive start
White's
throw and it's turned away for another
[Applause]
one Ben White looking for one of those
clever runs off him
again ht's on the move just inside the
penalty area
the guard's gone to the by line well
found good
throw another chance for
Nelson it's deflected behind it'll be a
corner I don't think he quite got a hold
of it well I was surprised it happened
was a minute ago exactly the same
throwing it was identical same run same
throw and that caused them a problem so
they shouldn't be done
twice Arsenal strong from set pieces
Gabrielle knows that all too well from
his goal from an erard free kick at
anfield just the other week Sak's Corner
help to cross cleared away from the goal
bit of a scramble in
there and arot going
away Diaz kept it
in sacka ard's touch
havs now shapes to shoot and Allison has
to get down and Arsenal on top here well
you mentioned it how good they were set
pieces there a wonderful ball in and
another great
opportunity this is the Liverpool way
when they get the ball they get on with
it Allison's had a test or two
[Applause]
a bit more time now for Liverpool's
keeper looking for Joe Gomez but he
won't playar
sacka HTS will make qu work here
[Applause]
like that from Havoc mentioned about
erard not taking up the opportunity to
have the shot there's no he hesitation
from him in having his shot
[Applause]
sacka
Nelson Alexander Arnold engages with
help from
GPO evaded the them
both jinho finds
erard Diaz was back helping out the
defense here he is trying to keep the
ball he's done that somehow and he was
fouled well we spoke about it earlier
about Arsenal speaking to the guys about
them having the opportunities and the
chances but certainly not putting them
away well they've had two or three good
ones in the first 9 or 10 minutes
here I think that was a half chance that
not from uh from Havard but at least
he's not shying away from having a
poppet
[Applause]
goal kind of saaka just felt a bit of
contact on the back of his heel but
seems to be okay that was after the
challenge and the twoing and throwing
with ls Diaz it was 6 one half a dozen
of the other there was nothing in that
one has been playing with a an Achilles
problem for quite a while and he does
play every game for Arsenal actually
played 99 of the last 100 Premier League
matches incredible for a Winger too
brilliant and the number of times he
gets fouled as well how quick he is and
his ability and everything else that
goes with it yeah it's been highlighted
this week hasn't it with Arsenal
insisting that they didn't complain
directly oh they've got a chance here
another mistake from Liverpool and
they've got away with it for now it's
Ard oh he hit it too
hard still Liverpool struggling blocked
by Alexander Arnold and now it is away
how on Earth did Arsenal not
score Goodness Me doesn't that just sum
it up what we were
seeing I mean that was four chances
within 10 seconds wasn't
[Applause]
it General quaner slows things down
it's what he needs to do cuz there under
serious pressure
here towards Nunes turn safely is back
to
ramsdale
Rice
jinho I've said it already but there 11
and a half minutes gone Arsenal should
have at least three or four goals Now
Incredible amount of chances Liverpool
have been no iously slow Stars this
season same thing's happening again
Darwin Nunes surely is pulling saliva
down
there to
run yeah that was a foul wasn't it
there's
zaka AR still trying to get flowing down
the right again strong Tackle by Ben
White listen to the noise around the
ground they enjoyed that well they're
liking what they're seeing apart from
not putting the ball in the back of the
net everything else has been superb
their attitude their effort their
commitment and going into tackles and
that creating
chances even referee John Brook seemed
to be nodding his head in approval at
that
[Applause]
challenge this being a premier league
venue we do have the assistance of V
today although I know you enjoyed a
certain game yesterday for the lack of
it not only enjoyed it really enjoyed it
the Sunland Newcastle game with nov we
go refreshing how on Earth did this not
result in an Arsenal goal well how many
chances the bar the
blocks just incredible sackers Nick and
the ball did really well didn't he that
should have gone in that one should have
gone in
leis
Diaz
Jones now
carer just got to try and slow this game
down a little bit now Liverpool with the
pressure that they've been under try and
take the noise out with this
crowd not so long ago we didn't say that
about Arsenal did we
[Applause]
generald
qua gin rice he's the whistle go against
him barging in from
behind foul on
Jones
Elliot there's
mallister Alexander Arnold trying to
find Darwin Nunes Curtis Jones into
challenge it's a super Tackle by Nunes
GPO with the shift to
Elliot
Jones Alexander Arnold Jones can't get
to it Nelson B the way a good block you
could see exactly what Trent was trying
to do with the pass into
Jones soer Nelson good
defending well White against purple it
doesn't look like Arsenal V Liverpool
but it feels like it
[Applause]
saliva
rice out to
Kio ree Nelson seen plenty of it that
one didn't
stick's looking for a better ball in
from P wasn't he didn't think it needed
to be that
hard Arsenal without Alexander zenchenko
[Applause]
Theo tomasi's gone away to play at the
Asian cup with
Japan quarantine is out alone at real
Saucy dad so they have a a vacancy at
left back at the
moment really good clear that from Nunes
gakpo finds
Diaz Elliot to
gakpo
[Applause]
canate Liverpool trying to get into a
rhythm
Jones has just missed the
beat
sacka
erar
hbert Nelson Has
Kor ahead and
[Applause]
outside
jino just like Nunes before holding the
ball up k has got to do that
again this evening with being that lone
man up front when that ball goes in it's
got to stick to him he did really well
there Defenders got to decide whether
they go tight with him or on that
occasion drop off and let him have
[Music]
it
[Applause]
[Music]
Kate
[Applause]
cister Allison as cool as you like made
it look so
easy it's the another goalkeeper who's
played the pass of the match so far
though qua
Alexander
Arnold nicely collected by
Elliot
[Applause]
gakpo
Elliot
[Applause]
quansa canate Under Pressure now from h
it's good defending from Arsenal being
patient everyone sticking with their man
cuz Liverpool are looking for that
opening on the
charge want to retreat
now
white Geor
[Applause]
erard back with
SBA Kio
jinho time for Arsenal to have a spell
knocking it about to one another
jino's
game get it and give
it K
Nelson s back to Gabrielle
just looking on that left hand side for
arsal havs has gone to the left and
Nelson's come in the middle there to try
and make that similar sort of runs he
made in the first few minutes with that
wonderful pass from ramsdale ramsdale
has gone over the top again sacker has
to challenge for it and Gomez and quaner
in one another's
way
rice Nelson popped up in the middle
[Applause]
sacka Dean
rice Nelson in that hole again he's
certainly got the freedom to be able to
do that there's that run again here is
Ree Nelson who has scored a winning goal
against Liverpool for arel in the
past
[Applause]
sacka
erard and returned there was no way back
to Nelson not there
Gabrielle and Gomez can watch that one
out if he so
wishes oops who's he there he is we knew
he'd be here Ian Edward right
NBA smile right here on the
television never off the television
[Applause]
ker chip out just had enough to find
Trent Alexander Arnolds who's motoring
[Applause]
now and playing it through for Darwin
Nunes Lu Diaz in the middle but not
there Safety First is the approach taken
by Ben White Liverpool Corner what about
the first touch there from Tren to
receive the pass to put it in his path
and then the forward pass I thought
gakpo should have actually got in there
because it was a decent ball in in the
end from
[Music]
Nunes the Elliot's
Corner no Virgil Van Dyke to attack it
[Music]
[Applause]
today Elliot into just the right
area and it's wide and it was D Nunes I
think who got to it it was a good ball
in and a great leap you know from Nunes
to find himself in that space he looking
for the quality of the ball that
was certainly quality and the leap was
great but he just couldn't get the
direction on it it's a decent
chance he's only scored in one of his
last 14 Games Starting nine of
those was Burnley on boxing day and the
way that he took that goal shows that he
is a finisher
well his numbers should be a lot better
the number of chances that he had has
missed including that one
there but he doesn't shy away there
Nelson who went down in a little delayed
fashion after trying to take on Trent
Alexander
Arnold there's nothing in
that not at
all fairness to re Nelson I think he
tried to stay on his feet maybe just
always was off balance
[Applause]
here the talk about the
wayo sh went down on Year's Day for a
penalty don't have to go there do
[Music]
we can't get the smile off your face
after
yesterday know what you're up to there's
McAlister Alexander Arnold
B Nunes is making up the
ground and held away from it by civa who
stood strong great
defending quick composed he read it
really well no
Panic
Jones
Elliot
Nelson wants to stay to
clear what a season he's having
CRA been brilliant he
has I think when he first joined from
cetti and he was loan back and it looked
as though he might not ever get a break
for Arsenal now he's an absolute staple
of the team it's been magnificently
[Applause]
as John Brooks has uh given a free kick
and he wants a word with geino for the
show of descent which we might not have
heard but we certainly lit red
don't know what he's complaining about
because clearly you can see he's got
hold of his shirt it's a
[Applause]
foul I think we know will be taking
it Elliot has given the signal oh it
will be Elliot he lifted in nicely but
it's easy enough for
rep shown his authority in the
team H down the middle with
habits doesn't re
jart V cut it out on his way
back
gakpo successfully stalled by geino now
erard to try and push on for Arsenal
[Applause]
SBA
Gabrielle B white
[Applause]
R finds ree
Nelson
R white a little move infield away from
Gomez returned to him by erar this is
crisp this is
pacy good work from Arsenal sacka shot
in the end rather and does a bit of that
was brilliant movement from him when he
came inside just off the uh off the line
there to get the ball and he received
the ball and again and he's first touch
and the way Arsenal moved it around with
Pier because that's been one of the
criticisms I
think this season is that they haven't
done that enough just to upset teams
that little bit more so they can't go 2v
one I mean on that occasion it was
brilliant just a finish again it's a
tougher one that we've toughest one that
we've seen I think certainly the chances
that they've had but the way they moved
the ball to get there was a positive
mallister was in the way to take all the
sting off the
shot kaker has just had a change of
Footwear 22 years old and this is game
number 206 in an Arsenal shirt oh what a
player what an attitude I love it
brilliant great I love watching
him plays with such energy and
enthusiasm great
play Allison's looking for Darwin Nunes
saliva was with
him ginho given a bit of treatment by
Lis
Diaz and John Brooks has maybe done
Arsenal favor there they got on with it
quickly don't think they were going
anywhere with it and the ball was
rolling they'll have to do it
again m
was in the side when these two teams
last met in the FA Cup 2-1 Arsenal win
in
2014 Arsenal went on to win the cup
beating whole city in the
final the second second person to win
the cup as player and manager for
Arsenal after the great George
[Applause]
Graham H erar wants it pulled back here
he is but there was
Gomez
rice white to
sacka
erard good looking delivery's trying to
come in on it jinho rice HS it won't
break for Nelson Alexander Arnold is
there had a little stroll across his own
penalty area just for the fun of it been
so many good positions Arsenal without
putting it in the net that final piece
which is often the hardest but they
doing ever so well getting in there you
can't put it in the
[Applause]
net was that anything to do with the
fact they haven't got a genuine Striker
on the field or yeah absolutely yeah I
mean that's I think that's been a
problem for them this season we said
before the game that the numbers are
down in forward positions in almost
everything mallister dispossessed this
time ear guard pulling it back havoc's
taking his
time enough time for Liverpool to get in
the right place to block it again too
much time far too much time needed I
didn't think he needed the touch I mean
it's great pressing again from Dean rice
and the pass there from erard is to
switch it just got to hit it there's no
need to take a touch there the pass is
soft enough it's in his way just go and
hit it
somebody next to me would have
done he and Wright would have
done I just don't need that touch you're
not going to get the time to take an
extra touch on another one at this
level you're given an
opportunity just take it they are being
given opportunities so
many and B shout against Alexander
Arnold from Nelson and he got support
from his friends in the crowd but John
Brooks wasn't particularly place to see
it Nick Greenhouse is the assistant on
that side of the field he didn't see it
either there will be a Liverpool throw
saw
that was there anything to see this is
what they were booing
up just a
bit the two
[Applause]
hands
Gomez Nunes to try to put the pressure
on Gabrielle was up against him and
equal to
him
mallister just get the feel and it's
maybe one of those games where Arsenal
might just look back and think how on
Earth have we missed all those chances
and maybe punished it's often what
happens isn't it when a team has
dominated so much like Arsenal have you
may just regret
it Liverpool will come out and play and
have spells of dominance at some
point he's Curtis Jones
[Applause]
to Diaz Diaz has been followed by
rice
Jones excellent Midfield work Curtis
Jones
gako Diaz
[Applause]
Elliot didn't manage to keep
it hits didn't manage to get
[Applause]
through
Gomez beautiful take
down now Nunes trying to win a corner
and Sala wrapped his foot around to
prevent that
[Applause]
happening
rice almost presented did it to Jones he
is now after Ben White and taking the
ball from
him white then in his way and the
referee is going to give that as a free
kick to Liverpool and it was what a
lovely piece of skill that was from
Curtis Jones did really well to win the
ball back in the first place and then to
have the ability to just say where you
go flick it there just going to go
around you and Ben White's got no choice
but to bring him down and it was a
foul his J is now really finding his
feet as a senior Liverpool player three
goals in his last four games he's adding
goals to his
game he had a super season after
starring for England at the European
under 21s last
summer man of the match in the final
against
[Applause]
Spain it's about feeling part of the
first team isn't it feeling as if you
belong in there and that just doesn't
happen overnight it may take longer time
for some than others
but he's certainly shown his best
football now isn't he had a few injury
problems
[Applause]
too Alexander Arnold on the ball which
usually spells danger for opponents goes
deep with it in fact he goes under the
roof of the goal with it well that's one
he's had from the left and one from the
right and both of them have been
poor a little bit more encouragement for
Jurgen klopp who's not had a lot to be
encouraged about today so far
expect better from
him such as his high
standards Michael Thomas we've already
talked about that goal he scored for
Arsenal at anfield but let's not forget
he scored in na Cup Final for Liverpool
1992 first of two that Liverpool got
against
Sunderland cracker as well wasn't
[Applause]
it 206 games for Arsenal but then 163 in
a Liverpool
sh no bad Curry is
it what a player he
was it's up for grabs now what a line
that
was giv away to mallister Jones working
and scrapping but losing out that time
to
civa civa wondering where he should go
next it's erard he usually has an idea
before he gets the ball havit offside
[Applause]
it's really good work again from CA and
bringing the uh the ball out just don't
need to be offside there he is offside
when you can see right across the
prdge now tonight you can watch all of
the highlights from this and all of
today's FA Cup games on bbc1 10:30 and
you can watch every FA Cup goal on the
BBC sport website and
app I think there've been a few today
just waiting for one
here it should have been three or
four another offside this time a
Liverpool
[Applause]
One rice sacker as he timed his run well
the flag has stayed down for
now up against gz
gz stopped by the Liverpool number
two white erard able to turn Gomez is
back there the guards having a look
there wasn't a gap to go
for he's come closer than anybody with
that shot that smashed against the bar
earlier
on Nelson he's come close as
well rice F say shoot so he does
straight down the barrel
no problem that for
Allison he was invited to have a shot
and he didn't take any time to do that
but it wasn't the most difficult save
was it now is it starting to open up
Jones asking Nunes to run again CA has
the head start on
[Applause]
him back to ramsdale nicely sorted
out
erard being held on to by m free kick
Arsenal really good play again from Kai
HS because that's a tough thing to do I
said earlier about him having to bring
his teammates into the game by holding
that ball up no better example in him
doing it there Ard to
sacka hav has wandered into the
middle that's Ben
White he got a hold of that that sizzled
its way to Allison he did it was really
good defending from Gomez he was left
one V one wasn't he was sacker again
same thing happened a minute ago and he
stopped that but it falls to Ben White
who didn't need a second invitation
there to have a shot a good
[Applause]
effort strong hand from the Liverpool
keeper sacka to
deliver Arsenal have given their fans
everything but the goal so far
today Alison has stayed back and another
chance has gone begging havs heads wide
how many do they
need we know how strong Arsenal are at
set
pieces and again it's a good ball
in again you see a white shirt this time
H is
it climbs
above got to be on target another chance
big
chance that's one of the best yet
timing of the leap was excellent contact
with the ball
wasn't and Liverpool have made a bit of
a mess of
[Applause]
that Gerald quena needs a bit of
attention klopp is a little concerned by
it possibly because it was a mess of of
their own making
yeah yeah I mean how many chances do
atin lead you said it earlier about them
they've been superb up until the final
third haven't they in terms of creating
chances working the ball you can see
what the injury is there isn't
it that didn't look nice did it
no one those things that shouldn't
happen but does every now and again it's
a nasty one didn't
it rolled his foot over the
ball and everything momentarily went
into the wrong place
the nod of the head and the uh
encouraging words of the medical team
look as though he will be able to carry
on yeah it looks that way doesn't ity
when he did it Liverpool don't have
anything really as regards Center back
replacement they've got Luke Chambers
who's a left back stroke center back
fullback really
very young Liverpool
bench it's all they've got
left points throw
sacka stopped in his tracks Arsenal
fence feel unfairly by MC
Alister the referee
doesn't it's a rib Crusher for Baya
saaka well it's another throw in from
exact same
position might be different players but
that's a concern from
Liverpool three throws
they've had the ball it's been too easy
to find a
[Applause]
teammate mallister I don't think he's
full of Apes don't think he feels he has
to explain himself at
[Applause]
all another Arsenal throw and the p
struggling with those and they missed
out on the Run of Dean rice
there erard excellent work by rice erard
is tripped and Arsenal are looking to
end the first half strongly and get what
they will feel his deserved reward for
their performance well it was a free
kick I mean dean rice did really well to
keep the ball under serious pressure and
then erard gets a
foul they've had the ball they've
created the chances they've got the
backing but they haven't been able to
beat Allison
yet it's the hardest thing to do you
know put the ball on the
N are you wanting me to read out some
numbers not at
[Applause]
all it is the hardest thing to do
definitely sacka try and create yet
another Arsenal opportunity they all get
back on side and Allison can watch that
one so Trend Alexander Arnold hasn't
found his delivery boots today and nor
has beo
sacka I just thought that look just
before half time you're looking for a
nice quality ball in there we know as I
said set pieces that they are very good
at not on that
[Applause]
occasion looking for Darwin
Nunes civa
generally won
those and now Darwin Nunes is on the run
and ramale has seen him
coming good goalkeeping that not had a
lot to do in fact hardly anything he's
got to stay alive and alert and he was
there I think he saved anything has
he he that one great passle no
that
quansa Kate
[Applause]
mallister Quanza gives it away Nelson is
sharply on that erard HTS and HTS has
room
now straight at Allison and he took an
eternity about it
again well the Arsenal press has been
superb but their finishing has been
Dreadful again I thought he took too
long gakpo
just too high for Lis
[Applause]
Diaz he must be one frustrated
manager there's his touch there just
pushes him another two or three yards
wide which then gives the goalkeeper the
advantage CU The Wider you go the less
you've got to
AA and again I just think he got to take
it
early scored four goals in his nine
appearances he should have had two or
three
today here's
gakpo gakpo is getting away and he's got
support from Trent Alexander Arnold and
that's off the bar it bursts through
ramsdell's gloves both teams now have
shaken the crossbar well he didn't need
a second invitation to have a shot and
he didn't take too long to get his shot
away there his first touch is brilliant
and he hits it with the outside of the
boot doesn't it just s bending
away what a strike that
is a smile is back on the face of the
Liverpool
manager that's what can happen though
isn't it you have all those chances with
an Arsenal and should be four five up at
least think believe believe he lock that
the level maybe even better going into
the break we are moving into first half
additional time now just a couple of
minutes to be added on
TR Alexander Arnold the closest that
Liverpool have come to a goal
yet I think this is what Arsenal have
done really well they've pressed really
well as a team you know they've not gone
on in as individuals or ones and twos
they've gone as a team and it's worked
for them and they've caught Liverpool
out two or three
times more white shirts near him and
space
purple sliced out by Quant nice stayed
in Jones has managed to keep it in and
he's been robbed by
rice herard mallister is hacking away at
him and Liverpool get the
[Applause]
[Music]
throw Gomez with the throw
white nice puts it out for another
[Applause]
one
qua Alexander Arnold
[Applause]
be forced out of play Arsenal throw him
and they want to be quick about it it's
that press again HS is barged off the
ball there'll be a free kick to finish
the half for Arsenal really good work
from Arsenal really impressive putting
them under pressure not allowing
Liverpool to
settle then getting the
foul another opportunity to put the ball
in the box from another set
piece and anfield on these Saturday
Before Christmas it was erard into the
box from a free kick and Gabrielle
header into the net this time it's ree
Nelson to take for
Arsenal everybody's back for
[Applause]
Liverpool right at the back of the
line won't reach
him and it is halime at the
Emirates and Arsenal have had the better
of it with nothing to show for him
Martin erard possibly hit the ball too
well in the midst of a scramble in the
Box he hit the bar and then just a few
moments ago Trent Alexander Arnold smash
one against the Arsenal crossbar ree
Nelson Has Come Close as well very early
on thanks to a long ball from Aaron
ramsdale incredibly Arsenal haven't
managed to score and it is still
goalless at the break it is Arsenal nil
Liverpool
nil met in the 1980 semi-final and it
went to three replays before Arsenal W
through to meet West Ham at
Wembley well we might be bound for one
replay this year unless one of these
teams can find a way through in the next
45 minutes both teams will not want a
replay that'll be the winter break kaios
absolutely
towards
[Applause]
havo with a chip back to
Nelson Nelson Hemm in and loses out to
mallister I think from a Liverpool point
of view there's no doubt Klo will demand
more intensity and for people to be
brave on the ball and get it under
pressure and try and handle that press
that Arsenal did ever so well in that
first half
Dean
rice
jinho Kor pulled away from the ball by
Luis
Diaz just looking at Liverpool as well I
think Nunes has gone onto that left hand
side and GAP fored gone down the
middle very fluid ahead of Alexis
mallister they can all go wherever they
want to roam really for Liverpool
[Applause]
no mo Sal remember
for well at least a month You' think
Egypt would expect to go far in the
Africa Cup of Nations in the Ivory
[Applause]
Coast no muhamad El neni for Arsenal in
their squad and wato Endo is absent for
Liverpool and Takira tomasu for Arsenal
there at the Asian cup no free kick
there as hav went
[Applause]
down y he's had his chances in that
first half Kai HZ didn't
he more shots than anybody else with no
success
[Applause]
this is a player who got the only goal
in the Champions League final Once Upon
a
Time he can score Under Pressure all
[Applause]
right just hasn't done it enough has
he back with
Allison here's canate
was pressur into playing that ball
aimlessly out of play it's going to be
an Arsenal
[Applause]
throw you mentioned 1971 a few moments
ago there's the the great man who kept
goal then Bob Wilson serve Bob Wilson
should be lovely
man football and broadcasting Legend
[Applause]
now was growing up a presented Football
Focus which is 50 this
[Applause]
year Saka racing onto it and he's got a
head start
too Saka tries to turn he managed it
Gomez just stayed in his way
sufficiently oh what a wonderful run
that was he just he actually went short
first of all You' see him there you
watch him go there you go into his own
half and he timed the run to Perfection
one run for the defender one for himself
to keep him on side and just didn't have
enough to get
away got Paul Tri and create something
of their
own Elliot round the back of
Jones it's Gomez having a
go he will score for the Liverpool one
day he's done that quite a lot in recent
weeks this is his 199th appearance for
the club and so far
nothing wasn't a bad effort was it
wasn't bad at
[Applause]
all imagine playing 199 games without
scoring a single goal
Alan went five or six once well that's
Martin later
cleared by ramster two years with no
goals for
England you did just before
96 stayed in the side though
just we're looking at FA Cup goals and
Allen got 27 in his
career almost won every other game how
many did Lin get 14 that was one every
other game how many did Murphy get also
14 ah okay who wants to win his
medal there's
Jones Martin by the way didn't score in
the FA Cup in 60 games but he did stop
150 goals got sent off 18 times there's
jinho
[Applause]
[Music]
there's
mallister now Elliot and Luis Diaz had
made a really good break and was well
founded look at Darwin Nunes that's what
Lu Diaz was trying to do now he might do
it by
himself lost
it but caught in two mins in the end but
that first ball that he tried to cross
should have been better into Nunes as he
made the run in there here is Nunes and
Diaz
again P looking to be more of an
attacking Force this half they've got to
be yeah much better from
Liverpool
intensity hitting them on the break with
numbers and you can just see him look up
there didn't he tried to he saw the pass
but he just couldn't finish it
off he does know whether to pass it or
get his shot away and then the numbers
are back for
Arsenal but more intent from Liverpool
[Applause]
Allison seeking out Luis Diaz he appears
to be the target for every pass now he
holds off one
challenge Darwin
Nunes can have a look at goal now no
there was no
way Jones can but he was leaning back as
he got it and that's the result well
again much better from Liverpool more
direct Pier running in in behind there
from Diaz I could see what Jones was
trying to do there but that's a long
ball in behind Diaz did really well to
keep it alive I could see what Jones was
trying to do he's just trying
to whip it into that far Corner keep it
low he's leaning
back putting the pressure on ramale
there and making him
hurry
white here's her a guard from sacka
flick
herard Jones away with the ball AR's
captur tries to rid him of it John
Brooks is happy with all the challenges
let the game go nicely the
ref been anything to trouble himself
[Applause]
with better from Liverpool isn't it
much Alexander
Arnold here's Darwin Nunes who's more
involved since going onto that Left
Flank cutting in here he
goes Darwin Nunes hits it and it flashes
past ramale and the look on his face
suggest that was close that that switch
has been key I said it just after
halftime with him going on to the left
hand side it's given them more Pierce
down there certainly more options to uh
to find him and you can tell by his
reaction how close that is it's a clever
ball in behind and you know as soon as
he gets that you think he's going to try
and work it on his right foot and that's
exactly what he
did I just waiting for the net to move
you can see more from this angle how
close it was
Nelson leis Diaz puts him off balance
and shoulder to shoulder again it's
going to be a free
[Applause]
kick he's claiming that it was a good
old shoulder charge from the both of
them think it was wasn't it I think it
was certainly wasn't my year
anyway so Aral
theyve been given the chance once again
to put pressure on that Liverpool
penalty
[Applause]
area Gabrielle has taken up residence in
front of
[Applause]
Allison we know where this is supposed
to
go Nelson little flatter with that
erard rice closed by
McAllister rice wins round two but
there's LS Diaz trying the first time of
a
gakpo Down goes erard nothing wrong with
that right under the ref
knows Darwin
Nunes just trying to find half a yard
out the room that looked a good tackle
brilliant tackle erard oh the game's
fizzing now it's
open you attack we attack this is what
we wanted to
see Darwin Nunes gakpo waiting and Nunes
went for goal there was no way pass
white just waiting for the Gap to for it
wasn't in
Nunes Quanza
FR a forced back over halfway by
erar arsal fans feel that's the queue
for their backing to be
needed and Allison has put it
out
moinho blocked by mallister free kick
Arsenal
[Applause]
you can hear what the Arsenal fans
thought of that
[Applause]
tackle T isn't it timed it to Perfection
again well everything you were saying
about William cber at the start of the
game has rung true he's been absolutely
spoton no room for error with those
tackles got to be right and that one was
ard's on the
[Applause]
ball oh they've deceived Liverpool here
and it's HTS with the Chip And Over the
Top how many more chances are Arsenal
going to pass up well it's an really
clever well-worked free kick from
Arsenal because all the Liverpool
players were expecting that ball to come
in and so were we to expect not God to
whip it in but the run is so clever off
havs because he shapes to go actually in
there and it was a good ball across he
just couldn't get his body over it could
he
sacka well could Gabrielle have headed
it
in just wonder whether he just got the
call to leave it but don't know why you
would just couldn't get his body around
it sacka could he but I think he could
have threw himself at that couldn't he
he's just waiting for Gabrielle to plant
that one off his forehead into the neet
double Liverpool change and there two
senior available substitutes are coming
on Cody gakpo makes way Doo sh will come
on he's got a great record against
Arsenal eight goals against him in the
past and Alexis mallister is off as well
he's only just coming back from a knee
problem and Ryan grenberg will take over
in
Midfield they're positive changes made
by urgen klopp yes they are
it's certainly been a positive start of
the second half from Liverpool anyway I
know that Arsenal just had had
opportunity but it's been better from
[Applause]
Liverpool and a play off Dogo jot
that'll be an Arsenal throw and I want
to get on with
it stand up for the Arsenal is the chant
around the ground
they've been very chatty with you today
haven't they nice really
[Applause]
nice and a playoff
Graber I think almost like for like both
substitutes W they B will go straight in
there there for Callister and J will go
straight up the
Middle where gakpo was there's
Nelson run into Alexander Arnold who's
now putting the pressure on
Gabrielle Sala finds
jinho erard managed to hold off the
challenge of quaner and this room down
the left now
Nelson HTS herard moving in the middle
and it's looping over Allison there's
Sucka oh
dear just took the deflection didn't it
there and Allison scrambling
back again down the left hand side work
it well good run again from H and
there's the little deflection I was on
about and Allison had to get a
touch you're just thinking for sacka to
come
and pull it back there he just he just
couldn't do it
I it come off the tour rather than the
front of the boot and you can see the
reaction there from the Arsenal
bench it's enough even to turn Mikel
Etta
gray sacka erard through htz canate
beats him to it oh it's on it's on now
and we said both teams wouldn't want to
draw and it looks as if they're going
for it now
[Applause]
ryce loses the ball that doesn't happen
often sacka wins it back but Liverpool
have it once again and Darwin Nunes has
lost it HTS
erard tight spaces for Arsenal sacka
found a way through to
erard and erard tries to win a corner he
hasn't Managed IT
[Applause]
I
mentioned the timing of tackles being
extremely important for those
Defenders a couple a did can and the
Arsenal fans wanted a corner for that so
did he Captain was
Adam Arsenal change re Nelson is coming
off Gabriel Martinelli the regular on
the left hand side is going to replace
him re Nelson he's only come off the
bench in the Premier League this season
nine times game time has been limited
but Mar he's taken to his task pretty
well but this just feels like the right
time to get Martin Elli on yeah little
bit of quality and bit of Pierce down
there play who scored at home and away
against Liverpool last season and has
got four goals against them in
all and he was the player who made the
difference in one of the big Premier
League clashes here in October with the
only goal against Manchester City
hooks away just wonder what edian K is
thinking on the bench with the number of
chances that his team has
created I think he's stewing a bit just
a
[Applause]
bit
toinho sacka erard he's trying to pull
all the
strings yeah he's playing really
well Martinelli a great Roar greets his
first two touches he nearly got through
and Elliot got
lucky there's a bout of wrestling going
on between Gabrielle and
[Applause]
jot I think there might be a bit of fire
in this before the
end Darwin
Nunes promising for Liverpool Elliot
joins in jot wants it Elliot has gone
straight to ramale it's how he wanted
it I thought about having a shot with
the left foot but then K back inside on
his right foot and just couldn't
generate the power to trouble the
goalkeeper Alexander Arnold Darwin Nunes
isn't going to get
[Applause]
there I think that's intier there isn't
it that just put his head down yeah
he'll be thinking with a number of
chances that we've created today just
for a moment I thought Eddie was getting
ready
[Applause]
what more animation though from miketta
now he's kicking every ball down
[Applause]
there back from Jones here's
n
[Applause]
Jones
J go shter was being held on to by
saliva and we're going to get the first
yellow card of the match
[Applause]
that's what Liverpool have done better
this half I said they had to be brave in
possession and try and get through the
Arsenal press by not being afraid to get
on the ball and they certainly did that
then and they've got themselves a free
kick got to do more of
it caution which is the first blot on
William ca's copy
[Applause]
book in F three up to them yeah
Alexander
Arnold
[Applause]
quansa
Saka not able to carry it
[Applause]
clear oh there was a ball on just for a
moment there and here's Elliot trying to
find the next one for Liverpool it's
Nunes is possessed by
Gabrielle
Martinelli invited to
move taking on canate got himself a
little bit of room Gomez couldn't dly
sacka was straight away in on
him
rice
jinho sacka
leaves it for Jones to
clear Saka was just trying to pick his
head up and find Ard wasn't he he
couldn't get the ball into
him
[Applause]
rice nice little edging possession of
the ball
[Applause]
I think you said Liverpool have been
brave in possession as well but what
they're also doing is is when they're
defending they're actually being brave
and leaving another two or three men
further forward so on the break they're
looking much more of a threat but that
means that they're going to leave gaps
at the back as well with a lack of
numbers there's Martinelli taking on
Alexander Arnold and getting past him
canate stationed just
right Diaz
Martinelli undoubtedly is going to add
something to Arsenal
now
jinho here is Martinelli and again he's
passed Alexander Arnold and once again
it's canate who stops him yeah that's
what you call back on your teammate up
Trent was done through the legs great
play for Martinelli and you're looking
for a little bit of help from your
fellow
Defender that's exactly what he got from
Kar a great
defender Martinelli has come on in just
the right mood that you want from a
[Applause]
substitute trying to draw the ref's
attention to the attention that he's
getting it's a disappointing corner from
Martinelli
disappointing his code for something
else
obviously jinho
Martinelli won't get to that that is
much better there's nothing more
frustrating for Defenders when they've
come all that way up from the halfway
line you're looking for a good quality
ball in and certainly to beat the
front man at that post and when they
don't do it it's very
frustrating penny for his thoughts and
his it's not that bad mate come
[Applause]
on well they're enjoying the
action but a lot of those Arsenal fans
have be wondering how on Earth the score
is still nil
nil Elliot they might hope that it
remains nil nil now it's Darwin Nunes
with L Diaz in support and it's behind
[Applause]
him
Diaz down no free kick rightly saw as
well now he's after the KE he looks
intend on Revenge cleared by
Gabrielle what is the problem here jinho
that will be a free kick caught by
Elliot is going to get a yellow card for
that wave of the arm yeah no you can't
do
that frustration coming to the four in
both
camps well I don't it wasn't the foul
that he got the caution for it was
reaction
[Applause]
that was a good opportunity wasn't it
Nunes and Diaz getting a touch of the
arsenals in that box again I mean it
just sums up this game doesn't it is
that just a lack of quality today in the
final third I didn't think it was a
difficult pass from him I mean did ever
so well to get in to that position in
the first
place oh for Ian right and Ian Rush
[Applause]
over John Barnes and John Barnes oh what
a player John Barnes
was all the top music artists are here
today John Barnes Gary barow hean
Right One by
[Applause]
oart zaka
renberg wins the ball for
[Music]
Liverpool normally you would say after
70 odd minutes it's nil nil it's not
been a great
game but I think with the chances that
we've had and some of the play I think
it's been a very entertaining game and
it's on the edge which always brings its
own
excitement don't forget you can see all
of the FA Cup highlights there are goals
elsewhere and there may well be some in
this one yet 10:30 BBC One and you can
watch every FA Cup goal on the BBC sport
website and
app
sh over Alexander Arnold Martinelli
brought the ball under his spell just
beautifully Shame about the pass that
followed kenberg it's behind Elliot rice
anticipating where that was going here's
sacka sack's had a go and he's off
beam again I could see exactly what he
was trying to do she's trying to whip it
into that far Corner which of course
we've seen him do so many
times not been his best today has he
47 Arsenal
goals nine this
season he might yet be the man who makes
the difference today
[Applause]
yeah do still have Eddie and K who we've
mentioned the Andre trossard as well
who's good for a goal or two he's got
them against Liverpool in the past
Alexander Arnold gets it back to Allison
and got a little whack for his trouble
from
[Applause]
havitz
Jones Nunes
B white a
beat can't do
it Saka with the whack away oh it's
better than that but it is hand ball
Martinelli trying to bring it down was a
little unlucky well you can tell by his
reaction can't you that he knew that he
was going to give a foul against him
handall
[Applause]
Jones Alexander Arnold
nearly through to LS
Diaz
Kate
[Applause]
Elliot leis Diaz has caught Gabrielle
there it's a painful
[Applause]
one good to see him getting up straight
here boot to boot
don't think we could call them boots now
can we
[Applause]
shoes two Liverpool changes now these
are interesting Curtis Jones and Harvey
Elliot are being replaced by Conor
Bradley here's one for you Al Bobby
Clark son of Lee son of your old
Newcastle marcker Lee Clark here he is
it's his third appearance for Liverpool
it's Connor Bradley's
[Applause]
ninth Saliba
erard HTS can't get it it's a good time
from CBA into erard just bypass that
Liverpool front three and the
Midfield we've pass 75 minutes now I
think it's probably incumbent on me
to say that a replay would be either a
week on Wednesday or a week on Thursday
at
anfield and neither team want it really
but they want it more than going out of
the cup yeah absolutely I mean I know
Liverpool have got a game this week
semi-final but
then both teams might have to cancel a
few days away the break that they might
be
planning can clpp will be on to the
travel agent in the
morning might not be any break after
Fulham in the League Cup semi-final
first leg on Wednesday not much of a
break for Liverpool anyway this month in
truth so weekend off they would take it
that's for sure
that's a telling number
yeah they're a threat and they're gone
for
it lipol do like to score late here's
Dio jot and he's got a little bit of
room to wle it through to Diaz and
ramsdale has made the save of the match
it's pretty much the first proper save
he's had to make it's a beauty it was a
beauty absolutely downlo to his right
hand side good flick on
from Nunes and jot picks it up it falls
kindly Di and oh what a save that is a
great strike as well thought it was
going in the bottom corner but he's down
so
quick it's how Lu Diaz takes the shot on
as well it comes through the legs he's
done well to see that and react like
that brilliant save not only that but to
get it out in the strong enough hand to
push it out for a corner y CL like the
attack back from his team now Alexander
Arnold to take the corner and Diogo jot
to lead for it ramale beaten and that
one's
white that looked like a big Miss by
Darwin
Nunes cannot believe how many chances
both teams now have had in this game and
the leap first of all the leap there
from jotter it is that there then to get
the
direction hits the ball there but then
it falls to Nunes and it's a good touch
we just can't guide it into the corner
what he's trying to do but that leap
there from jotter It's a Wonderful
header sort of hanging in the air wasn't
hez has landed on canate and no genuine
attempt to win the ball in the air
though 179 Arsenal lead on a Arsenal
lead on attempt so I suppose it matters
if you put the ball in there's not been
a lack of action in both goal mouss has
there just the back of the
net
[Applause]
Gomez Sak is holding on to him graen
bur erard hauls Graber to the floor and
just about resists the show of descent
just about kept a lid on it it's good
work from
grur did really well strong you can see
ard's got hold of him there and he turns
him and puts her through his legs and it
is a
foul Alexander
Arnold Ready
to test Arsenal again and it was from
his last delivery that jota hit the bar
and Nunes fired wide
is it going to happen for
one or the other of these Giants of the
English game and this
competition Alexander Arnold it's in
this time Liverpool find a way and it's
leis Diaz who leads the way to the
Liverpool
supporters what a ball in that is we
said about in the first half there were
a couple occasions there he disappointed
in his delivery not on this occasion TR
and where do you want it right in the
middle that's exactly where he put it
you can see the reaction from him
absolutely yeah quality ball can someone
get on the end of it it's an own goal
pretty sure it's an own goal you
know I think
it's I think this goes in off The
Unlucky yakob K
yeah there we go
it's incredible isn't it all the chances
that have been created and it's a own
goal but the ball in from Trent was
superb it just puts them under
pressure was Diaz that jumped in front
of him and Kio didn't see it coming
nothing ramsdale could do and look at
that we got a triple fist pump from
Jurgen
[Applause]
Klo another goal made by the W of a
right foot that belongs to Trent
Alexander
Arnold Arsenal nil Liverpool one and
that after all those Arsenal chances in
the
match we said it didn't we the may live
to regretting and at the minute they
certainly are the chances that they've
had Arsenal that can only blame
themselves at the minute how many times
does this
[Applause]
happen Clark
was an Arsenal change and a change we
expected in the aftermath of the goal
Eddie and ker on for
xino Alexander
Arnold Nunes that will fall for
him Nunes has support from Gomez he's
got Luis Diaz there too he had to dig at
it really good play again from Kate
winning the ball timing his tackle
superbly well which puts Liverpool again
on the front
foot got a really good game Kate he been
under huge pressure at
times so edian kti has been given eight
minutes and a little bit more to rescue
Arsenal's FA Cup
[Applause]
hopes worth a trick it always
is you got to see well done to Liverpool
at this moment in time for the way
they've actually bounced back because
they were pretty awful in the first half
other than that Trent attempt to hit the
bar been much better second off here's
Diaz
Bradley Conor Bradley's introduction has
allowed Alexander Arnold into that
Midfield roll a little bit
more really surprised that it's taken
this long to bring in K on particularly
with the number of chances arsenal were
creating he erard
sacka they have a genuine Striker on the
field now in entia and erard is fouled
by Darwin Nunes free kick for
[Applause]
Arsenal you got to see well done for
Nunes coming back and tracking back and
working for his team but not forgiving
the foul away in such a dangerous
position
[Applause]
there
guard here's the
Craftsman and it comes from the captain
Oh it needed a flick towards goal and it
didn't get one and it's behind for a
goal kick he's not happy he thinks it
was a corner wasn't he looking for again
a quality ball in there don't don't
think it was a bad
[Applause]
one 6 minutes of the 90 to go and there
are a few geers because Allison will
take his time now of course he
[Applause]
will yeah try and see the game
out it's what most teams or all teams do
when they're winning with a few minutes
left fre kick Liverpool
Dio shot was being lent upon but they
were a little too hasty
there Alexander Arnold grenberg he's
made a difference it's coming
up Darwin Nunes
[Applause]
J
canate nobody getting onto that
lift Liverpool have got some serious
grit about them this season even when
they're not on top of their game they
stay in the game yeah absolutely I mean
see what you want about the chances that
Arsenal have missed and we can be
critical of them for that but in terms
of a Liverpool
performance they've had to
be patient and they've had to stick
together it's been tough at times but
that what that's what good teams do that
said they're not over the line yet
Bradley cl to LS Diaz
[Applause]
Gabrielle mentioned Liverpool's
propensity to score late goals Arsenal
managed four premier league wins with a
goal in the 85th minute or later this
season and they've got the
support just need to find the quality in
front of gol Martinelli robbed by
Bradley yeah well done really well done
he still up well there to
[Applause]
Martinelli there's Liverpool's record
since the first of April last year when
they've scored first in a match they
don't lose he T to
win they're pretty good at coming back
when they go behind as well
[Applause]
Miss Diaz did well to keep the ball away
from Dean rice now here's Connor
[Applause]
Bradley J and Bradley too close to one
another
erard one back for Liverpool by
Alexander Arnold
[Applause]
brings that one down with
ease yeah it certainly wasn't an easy
one made it look easy but it wasn't two
Arsenal changes
happening can tell you that one is a
Smith row but we can't help you with the
numbers Andro TR are coming on as well
you can see those
numbers number 15
y by number 19 Leandra cha jaob Kio is
[Applause]
off Kai hav has made way as
well there's
[Applause]
Saka
rice Martinelli Bradley comes
close
rice 2 minutes of the 0 to go we wait at
the board with interest here's
sacka
erard in between trossard and
sacka he trying to be too intricate at
times aren't the Arsenal I think it's
really good play again in there that
final pass how many times we said that
this afternoon
[Applause]
SBA Knocked Down by Bradley Clark to J
and away from Alexander Arnold Liverpool
are sitting back now they're looking to
hold on to what they've got what they've
got at the moment is a Passage through
to the fourth
[Applause]
round Martin Elli
Gabrielle white erard collects erard is
taken
out yellow card grenberg free kick
Arsenal yeah it was one of those clever
passes
again and also a decision that he's got
to make and he thinks the right decision
that he has to do is foul him and bring
him down and take a yellow
God now what have Arsenal got from
here I think it's the most Central free
kick we've seen all
[Applause]
game well they need one here more goals
from set pieces than anyone this
season does erard take the direct
route looks as though he's going to try
and seek somebody out in the middle
[Applause]
Ard and it comes and behind it goes from
Darwin Nunes just for a moment the eyes
widened he didn't know where it was
going well I didn't know where it was
going either not sure he did in the
end Goodness Me Too Close for
Comfort Martinelli to throw it in there
[Applause]
Allison trying to fight his way through
to the
[Applause]
ball no Panic with that one with the
Nunes though that was a great header
defensive header now Liverpool might
have a break on they do have a break on
it's
Diaz two over Diaz gets through and
ramale pounces on the
ball the ball when it did go up said
four more
minutes here's rice he's been fouled by
Clark he's going to get a booking
yeah I know people don't like it don't
like to hear it but he had to do it for
the sake of his
team his dad gave a few away there those
as well important
[Applause]
ones
Saka just a little toe to it prevented
the ball from going cleanly through
to her guard here's Gabrielle and now
[Applause]
Martinelli want to get your player of
the match soon Alan but I'm Lo to ask
you just at the
moment give me another
[Applause]
minute thr couldn't get the ball down
sacka does high up on the
chest Ben
White and Bradley heads behind Arsenal
corner here they come again well done
Connor Bradley really good defendant
Staying Alive
alert doing his
job know have conceded a corner but he
had to do
that well it's going to happen
[Applause]
now another one into the box and Allison
has it and Alis
will hold it brilliant goalkeeping take
the pressure off your Defenders just
what you need as a Defender where are
your goalkeeper come and help us out
that's exactly what he did and there's
my man of the match
katti there he was but we had to leave
him because towin Nunes is on the
ball
Bradley Bradley puts it in and it's
cleared by S but terrific little Cameo
at right back from Connor Bradley he
done well hasn't he done a really good
job and looked impressive when he's come
on play for Bolton wanders last season
he was their player of the year and I
know Jurgen klopp was watching him very
closely very highly
rated yellow card for Trent Alexander
Arnold in the midst of all
that well now you can tell us why
there's my man of the match without his
normal partner van djk today he's had to
stand up he's had to be the leader at
the back and I think he has he's made
some impressive tackles and he's been
under huge pressure at
times can he see Liverpool
through no option roard other than back
to ramsdale Arsenal have seconds
now ramale looking for just the right
ball now it's a case of everyone
challenge for
it and Liverpool win it and Darwin Nunes
will run with it Doo tells him where to
go
next look at the purple shirts now and
it's Lis Diaz and he sealed it by
Smashing the ball into the roof of the
Arsenal net oh what a clever finish that
is we spoke so many times this game
about players taking extra touches
touches that they don't need none of
that then he takes the One Touch pushes
it out his feet and gets his shot away
and ramsdale has got no chance goes in
in the back of the net Liverpool hit
them on the break Arsenal committing men
forward as they had to
do Liverpool worked it really well and
he can be delighted
Club Liverpool are on their way into the
fourth round of the FA
Cup and that switch has worked perfectly
for Liverpool with new has on the left
hand side come doing that from the
second half and just thinking the touch
there take it early the one touch and
out of your feet and get your Striker
with what you've got to do he did it so
well ramsdale has got no
chance that is how to finish it's
finished the Cup tie once and for
all when they had to commit men forward
didn't they
Arsenal Liverpool are going to push
forward as a Chase of whether they're
going to go into the corner and protect
what they've got try and get that second
one all
over for Arsenal this is the one that
got away so many chances in the first
half of the match in particular they
couldn't take any Liverpool stayed in it
yes they rode their luck early on but
then they found a rhythm and Alan they
found a way as they so often do that's
what good teams do and that's what good
managers do they spot the problem and
Jurgen did that at halim and he switched
Nunes onto the left hand
side and they look so much more of a
threat in that second